잠깐
Stop.
하지마 이건 옳지 않아
We can't do this. It's not right.
쉘든 두가지 길이 있어
Sheldon, you have two choices.
티보 안에 더 큰 하드 드라이브를 집어넣게 하거나
ther you let him put a bigger hard drive in the TiVo,
마을로 나가기 전에 안의 내용을 다 지우는거지
or you delete stuff before we go out of town.
하지만 박스를 열게 되면 보증이 무효가 되
But once you open the box, you've voided the warranty.
보증, 그것은 제조자에게로 연결되는 성스러운 맹약이지
The warranty is a sacred covenant we've entered into with the manufacturer.
그는 그의 기계를 고치려 할것이고 우리는 그에게 기계를 보내주는거지
He offers to stand by his equipment, and we in return
하드웨어의 통일성을 해치지 않는다는 약속을 하면서말이야
agree not to violate the integrity of the internal hardware.
이 작은 오렌지색 스티커가 우리를 갈라놓는 유일한 존재야
This little orange sticker is all that stands between us and anarchy.